Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Penna. R.R. 93598, 93605, 93736, 93749 (Box 136, Folder 13)
- Penna. R.R. 93750, 93806, 93807, 93881 (Box 136, Folder 14)
- Penna. R.R. 93942, 93969, 93970, 94010, 94266 (Box 136, Folder 15)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. 89535, 90275, 90454, 90729 (Box 136, Folder 16)
- Penna. R.R. 94329, 94351 (Box 136, Folder 17)
- Penna. R.R., N.Y.C.R.R., C.T.&D. R.R. 88636, 88776 (Box 136, Folder 18)
- Penn Central 94512, 94513, 94514, 94910, 94741, 94904, 94798 (Box 136, Folder 19)
- Penn Central Co. A. 95386 (Box 136, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. 87728 (Box 136, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. 87788, 87791, 87979, 88721 (Box 136, Folder 22)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. 91684, 94127, 94128, 94129 (Box 136, Folder 23)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. 94130, 94131, 94132, 94133 (Box 136, Folder 24)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. 94134, 94135, 94136, 94137 (Box 136, Folder 25)
- Pittsburgh & Shawmut R.R. 92961 (Box 136, Folder 26)
- Pittsburgh & West Virginia R.R. 90824 (Box 136, Folder 27)
- Reading Co. R.R. A.86763, A. 86765, A. 86766 (Box 136, Folder 28)
- Reading Co. R.R. A.86769 (Box 136, Folder 29)
- Reading Co. R.R. A. 86772, A. 86773 (Box 136, Folder 30)
- Reading R.R. 87544 (Box 136, Folder 31)
- Reading R.R. 88511, 88633, 88952, 89122 (Box 136, Folder 32)
- Reading R.R. 94627, 94694, 94826, 94831, 95072 (Box 136, Folder 33)
- Reading R.R. 89835, 89853, 90020, 90092 (Box 136, Folder 34)
- Reading R.R. 90167, 90168, 90169, 90198 (Box 136, Folder 35)
- Reading R.R. 90349, 90371, 90418, 90423 (Box 136, Folder 36)
- Reading R.R. 90432, 90510, 90584 (Box 136, Folder 37)
- Reading Co. 90592, 90651, 90692, 90696 (Box 136, Folder 38)
- Reading R.R. 90924, 90946, 91078, 91221 (Box 136, Folder 39)
- Reading R.R. 91295, 91365, 91366 (Box 136, Folder 40)
- Reading R.R. 91403, 91542, 91739, 91879 (Box 136, Folder 41)
- Reading R.R. 91905, 92158, 92184, 92383 (Box 136, Folder 42)
- Reading R.R. 92530, 92526, 92544, 92557 (Box 136, Folder 43)
- Reading R.R. 92621, 92822, 93180, 93193 (Box 136, Folder 44)
- Reading R.R. 93292, 93311, 93342, 93358 (Box 136, Folder 45)
- Reading R.R. 93917, 93954, 94256, 94288, 94608 (Box 136, Folder 46)
- Western Maryland R.R. 91293, 92000, 92022, 93454 (Box 136, Folder 47)
- Western Maryland Railroad Company 94149, 94850, 95031, 95043 (Box 136, Folder 48)
- Reading R.R. 93385, 93398, 93399, 93620 (Box 136, Folder 49)
- B.&O. R.R.- Unsafe conditions on the Berlin Branch in Somerset County (Lodge #218) (Box 137, Folder 1)
- B.&O. R.R. Unsafe Operating Practices at East Side Yard, Phila., Pa. (Lodge #953) (Box 137, Folder 2)
- Bus & Taxi Cab Regulations- Proposed Amendment to Rule 17(h) (Box 137, Folder 3)
- D.&H. R.R.- Removal of Brakemen (Lodge #94) (Box 137, Folder 4)
- Dept. of Highways- Exemption from Part III of Commission's Railroad Regulations to permit the construction of crossing where track of Norristown Junction Branch of Reading Company Will Cross Below Grade of Tracks of Schuylkill Valley Branch of P.R.R., in (Box 137, Folder 5)
- Department of Highways- Exemption from Part III of the Commission's Railroad Regulations to permit the Construction of the Crossing Where (1) the Northbound Lane of the Delaware Expressway, etc. (Box 137, Folder 6)
- Donora South R.R.- Abandonment of Entire Line in Donora and Carroll Township (Box 137, Folder 7)
- Elimination of Firemen- Various Railroads (Box 137, Folder 8)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Change in Status of Lake Ariel Station (Lodge #382) (Box 137, Folder 9)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Change in Status of Station in Lake Township, Wayne County (Box 137, Folder 10)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Change in Status of Station in the Borough of Pen Argyl, Northampton County (Box 137, Folder 11)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Change in Status of Station in the Boro. Of Thompson (Box 137, Folder 12)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.-Change in Status of Station in the Boro. Of Forest City (Box 137, Folder 13)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R. -Removal of Car or Cats on the Rear-End of Trains Behind the Cabin Car or Caboose (Lodge #142) (Box 137, Folder 14)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.-Switches -Meadville Yard (Lodge #142) (Box 137, Folder 15)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Public Crossing Near Scranton (Glasgow Inc.) (Lodge #382) (Box 137, Folder 16)
- Erie-Lackawanna R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Nashua, Pa., Nat'l Stone Co. (Lodge #142) (Box 137, Folder 17)
- McKeesport Conn. R.R. -Handling of Hot Metal Ladles in the Nat'l Tube Works (Lodge #534) (Box 137, Folder 18)
- Montour R.R. -Unsafe and Hazardous Conditions in Coraopolis Area at No. 4 Mine Hills and Champion Cleaning Plant (Lodge #310) (Box 137, Folder 19)
- New York Central R.R. Inadequate Service Being Rendered Shippers on the Cowanesque Valley Branch (Lodge #195) (Box 137, Folder 20)
- New York Central R.R.-Removal of Flagman on Certain Trains (Lodge #195) (Box 137, Folder 21)
- Penna. R.R. -Change in Status of Station in the Borough of Littlestown, Adams County (Lodge #1021) (Box 137, Folder 22)
- Penna. R.R. Complaints Relative to Trains F-94-95 and F-100-101 (Lodge #1021) (Box 137, Folder 23)
- Penna. R.R. -Consist of Train #60 (Box 137, Folder 24)
- Penna. R.R. -Crews Working Short Handed Altoona-Cresson (Lodge #498) (Box 137, Folder 25)
- Penna. R.R. -Discontinuance of Less-Than-Carload Freight Service at All of Its Stations in the City of Philadelphia (Box 137, Folder 26)
- Penna. R.R. -Discontinuance of Less-Than-Carload Freight Service at Various Pittsburgh Stations (Box 137, Folder 27)
- Penna. R.R. -Elimination of Marker Lights on Computer and Thru Passenger Trains, Pgh. Terminal and Weeds at Butler and Springdale Yards (Box 137, Folder 28)
- Penna. R.R. -Flasher Lights at Crossing on Route #65 at Ambridge, Pa. and Crossing at Stone-Mudge Co. on North Rochester Branch, New Brighton, Pa. (Box 137, Folder 29)
- Penna. R.R. -Lack of Rear-End Markers on Train #50 (Lodge #1010) (Box 137, Folder 30)
- Penna. R.R. -No Lighting at the North End of the West Brownsville Yard (Lodge #299) (Box 137, Folder 31)
- Penna. R.R. -"Operation Beaver" (Lodge #574) (Box 137, Folder 32)
- Penna. R.R. -Operation of Train #22 (Lodge #946) (Box 137, Folder 33)
- Penna. R.R. -Rear-end Collision Between Two Trains at Conway Yard (Lodge #345) (Box 137, Folder 34)
- Penna. R.R. -Rule #99 (Box 137, Folder 35)
- Penna. R.R. -Substituting Budd Multi-Unit cars on Trains #600, #604 & #605 (Lodge #574) (Box 137, Folder 36)
- Penna. R.R. -Switching Hazards -Altoona (Lodge #174) (Box 137, Folder 37)
- Penna. R.R. -Switch Lamps for the Yard at Thurlow, Chester, Pa. (Lodge #488) (Box 137, Folder 38)
- Penna. R.R. -Trainmen's Seats in Engine Cabs (Box 137, Folder 39)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe and Hazardous Conditions at Scully, Carnegie, etc. (Lodge #571 -Schafer & Wheatley) (Box 137, Folder 40)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions at the Lake Yard Office, Erie, Pa. (Lodge #199) (Box 137, Folder 41)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions -Pgh. Passenger Yd. (Lodge #309) (Box 137, Folder 42)
- Penna. R.R.-Unsafe Condition -Gallitizin to Altoona -Eastern Slope (Lodge #753) (Box 137, Folder 43)
- Penna. R.R.-Unsafe Conditions (Lodge #160) (Box 137, Folder 44)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions -Lodge #488 (Box 137, Folder 45)
- Penna. R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at North Side, Pittsburgh, Pa. Area (Lodge #299) (Box 137, Folder 46)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe Conditions at Petersburg, Roaring Spring & Bedford Branches (Box 137, Folder 47)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe Conditions at Thorndale, Earnest & Lancaster (Lodge #117) (Box 137, Folder 48)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe Conditions at Thurlow Yards and P.R.R. Tracks at Sun Oil Co. (Lodge #488) (Box 137, Folder 49)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe Conditions Existing on MUCars (Lodge #511) (Box 137, Folder 50)
- Penna. R.R.-Unsafe Conditions in East Brady, Rimersburg and Vicinity (Lodges #258 & #753) (Box 137, Folder 51)
- Penna. R.R.-Unsafe Conditions in Scully District (Lodge #571) (Box 137, Folder 52)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe Conditions in the Wilkes-Barre, Buttonwood and Honey Pot Areas (Lodge #153) (Box 137, Folder 53)
- Penna R.R.- Unsafe Conditions -N.Y. Region- N.Y. Dist. At Trenton, Morrisville, Bristol & Coalport Area (Box 137, Folder 54)
- Penna R.R.-Unsafe Conditions -Thurlow Dist., Chester, Pa. (Lodge #488) (Box 137, Folder 55)
- Penna. R.R. -Unsafe Conditions -U.S. Aluminum Corp. (Lodge #117) (Box 137, Folder 56)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. -Discontinuance of Passenger Station at Youngstown, Ohio, and Termination of Pgh., Pa. to Youngstown, Ohio train at Campbell, Ohio. (Box 137, Folder 57)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R.- Train #264- No Heat and Frozen Sanitary Facilities (Box 137, Folder 58)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie R.R. -Violation of Rule #9 in Rankin, Pa. (Lodge #632) (Box 137, Folder 59)
- Pittsburgh & Shawmut R.R. -Unsafe Conditions at Bridgeburg Brick Co., Agway Inc. & Cadogan Mines (Lodge #573) (Box 137, Folder 60)
- Reading R.R. -Automatic Block Signals (Lodge #541) (Box 137, Folder 61)
- Reading R.R. -Belt Line North Railroad- Hazardous Conditions at Various Public Crossings in the Philadelphia Area (Lodge #956) (Box 137, Folder 62)
- Reading R.R.- Change in Status of Station 23rd & Arch Sts. In the City of Phila. (Box 137, Folder 63)
- Reading R.R. -Collision of Jenkintown Shuttle Train & Reading Commuter Train at Spring Garden Street Station, Phila. (Box 137, Folder 64)
- Reading R.R. -Derailment of Passenger Train near Woodmont Station on the Newtown Branch on 3/14/64 (Box 137, Folder 65)
- Reading R.R. -Flashers Not Operating at Lititz, Pa. (Lodge #172) (Box 137, Folder 66)
- Reading R.R. -Switch Targets -Reading. Yard 9lodge #172) (Box 137, Folder 67)
- Reading R.R. -Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions at Belmont, Subway, and Wayne Junction (Lodge #131) (Box 137, Folder 68)
- Reading R.R. -Unsafe Conditions at Rubin's Scrap Yard, Lancaster, Pa. (Lodge #172) (Box 137, Folder 69)
- Reading R.R. -Unsafe Conditions at Willow Street Branch (Lodge #131) (Box 137, Folder 70)
- Union R.R. -Proposed Changes in Operating Practices (Box 137, Folder 71)
- Union R.R. -Unsafe Conditions of Blast Furnaces at Rankin, Pa. (Lodge #872) (Box 137, Folder 72)
- Union R.R. -Unsafe Condition of Moulds & Hot Ingots Being Moved On Ingot Cars Between Duquesne & Homestead (Lodge #997) (Box 137, Folder 73)
- Upper Merion & Plymouth R.R. -Weeds and Debris Along Tracks (Lodge #1079) (Box 137, Folder 74)
- Close Clearance- P.R.R. -11th St. & 11th Ave., Altoona, Pa. (Lodges 174 & 498) (Box 137, Folder 75)
- Close Clearances- P.R.R. -Ernest Yard (Lodge #117) (Box 137, Folder 76)
- Close Clearance -Union R.R. (Lodges #872, #997, #1018) (Box 137, Folder 77)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Finance Docket No. 21260 & 21294: Discontinuance of Trains Between N.Y.C., Buffalo, Suspension Bridge, N.Y., and Lehighton, Pa. (Box 138, Folder 1)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Installation of Reflector Discs on Switch Targets at Wilkes-Barre, Pa. (Box 138, Folder 2)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Maintenance of Switch Lamps in the City of Hazleton (Lodge #173) (Box 138, Folder 3)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- removal 3rd Brakeman- Allentown 5:45 Yd. Assignment) C. 17555 (Box 138, Folder 4)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Removal of Skateman from Hump Operation at Coxton Yards (Box 138, Folder 5)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Removal of Third Man on Mine Runs, Out of Coxton Yard (Lodges #189 and #153) (Box 138, Folder 6)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Rule 8, Part II, Railroad Regulations- Requesting Additional Time to Comply (Box 138, Folder 7)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions- Hazleton Shaft Colliery (Box 138, Folder 8)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Unsafe Conditions (Close Clearances, Weeds, & Wash-Outs) (Box 138, Folder 9)
- L.&; N.E. R.R. & C.R.R. of N.J.- Finance Docket Nos. 21155, 21154, and 21153- Abandonment- Entire Line and Purchase of Certain Portions of Line Proposed to be Abandoned by L.&N.E. (Box 138, Folder 10)
- McKeesport Connecting R.R.- Various Unsafe Conditions (Box 138, Folder 11)
- Monessen Southwestern R.R.- Pgh. Steel Co. (Box 138, Folder 12)
- Monessen Southwestern R.R.- I.D. 28 Soaking Pits (Box 138, Folder 13)
- Monessen Southwestern R.R.- Unsafe Conditions (Box 138, Folder 14)
- Monon. Ry.- Discontinuance of LCL in Fayette, Greene, & Washington Counties (Box 138, Folder 15)
- Monongahela Connecting R.R.- Trainmen's Room & Bldg. in Furnace Alley of Jones & Laughlin (Box 138, Folder 16)
- Montour R.R.- Discontinuance of Less-Carload Freight Serv. At All Stations on Its Lines (Box 138, Folder 17)
- New York Central R.R.- A. 86694 & A. 86697 Change in Agency Freight Stations- Snow Shoe & Jersey Shore, Pa. (Box 138, Folder 18)
- New York Central R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Winburne, Pa. (Box 138, Folder 19)
- New York Central R.R.- LCL Shipments (Box 138, Folder 20)
- New York Central R.R.- ICC Bs-Ap-No. 15002: Proposed Discon. Manual Block-Signal System, Beech Creek Branch, Syracuse Division (Box 138, Folder 21)
- New York Central R.R.- Unsafe Conditions Existing in the Erie Yard (Box 138, Folder 22)
- New York Central R.R.- Violation of Operating Rules (Kenefick, Chm., G.G.C., B.R.T., N.Y.C. R.R.) (Box 138, Folder 23)
- Nickel Plate R.R.- Various Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions at Erie, Pa.- Lodge #259 (Ohio) (Box 138, Folder 24)
- Non-Certificated Truckers- U.S. Steel Corporation (Box 138, Folder 25)
- P.B. & N.E. R.R. - Violation of Rule 8 (Switches) (Lodge #989) (Box 138, Folder 26)
- Penna. R.R. A. 83341 (30th Street P.O.) (Box 138, Folder 27)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Non-Agency Passenger Station at New Castle Jct. (Lodge #955) (Box 138, Folder 28)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Service and Removal of Track on Former Chartiers Branch (Lodge #571) (Box 138, Folder 29)
- Penna. R.R. Abandonment of Service on a Portion of the East Pittsburgh Branch Track (Box 138, Folder 30)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Service on H.&P. Branch Spur Track, Chapman Township (Box 138, Folder 31)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Service on Newtown Square Branch Spur Track, Grasstown (Box 138, Folder 32)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Spur Track- Meadow Lands and Zediker Branch Line (A. 88912) (Box 138, Folder 33)
- Penna. R.R.- Abandonment of Spur Track- Nescopeck Branch of Broad St. (A. 91394) (Box 138, Folder 34)
- P.R.R.- Abolition of Crossing 86835 & Portio of Siding 86836 Track (Spring City) (Box 138, Folder 35)
- P.R.R.- Bayard Branch, Pgh. Region, Unsafe Conditions (Box 138, Folder 36)
- Penna. R.R.- Block System at Tunnels (Box 138, Folder 37)
- Penna. R.R. Change in Agency Station at Clairton, Allegheny County, Pa. (Box 138, Folder 38)
- Penna R.R.- Change in Agency Station at South Greensburg, Westmoreland County, Pa. (A. 86286) (Box 138, Folder 39)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Bor. Of Bentleyville, Washington County (Box 138, Folder 40)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Cresson, Cambria County (A. 84673) (Box 138, Folder 41)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Franklin, Cranberry Township, from Agency Freight Station to Agency Carload Only Freight Station (Box 138, Folder 42)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Homer City, Indiana County (A. 84729) (Box 138, Folder 43)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station at Nescopeck, Luz. Cty. (Edelman) (Box 138, Folder 44)
- Penna. R.R. Change in Status of Station, Boro. Of Bedford, Bedford County. (Box 138, Folder 45)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station, Boro. Of Bentleyville, Washington County (Box 138, Folder 46)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station in Dillsburg, from That of an Agency Freight Station to That of an Agency Carload Only Freight Station (Box 138, Folder 47)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of its Station at New Brighton, Beaver County, Pa. (A.86057) (Box 138, Folder 48)
- Penna. R.R.- Change in Status of Station (Borough of Portage) (Box 138, Folder 49)
- Penna. R.R.- City of Phila. -Approval of Alteration & Reconstruction of Crossing Where Bridge Carrying Wissahickon Ave. Crosses Above Grade of P.R.R. -Exemption from Requirements of Part III of Commission's RR Regulations (Box 138, Folder 50)
- Penna. R.R.- Complaint on "Rollikron" Devices- Lodge #511 (Box 138, Folder 51)
- Penna. R.R.- Conemaugh Div. at Foxburg & Emlenton, Pa. -Use of a 19 Order to Eliminate the Necessity of a Flagman (Box 138, Folder 52)
- Penna. R.R.- (Conemaugh Division)- Kiski Jct.- Apollo Area- Herrs Island (Weeds & Need of Flood Lights) (Box 138, Folder 53)
- Penna. R.R.- Copperhead Snakes (Butler Secondary Track) Lodge #753 (Box 138, Folder 54)
- Penna. R.R.- Dept. of Highways- Grade Crossings- West Chester Boro., Chester County (Box 138, Folder 55)
- Penna. R.R.- Derailment of Train #601 at Lancaster, Pa. (Box 138, Folder 56)
- Penna. R.R.- Discontinuance of Handling Less-Than-Carload Shipments (Box 138, Folder 57)
- Penna. R.R.- Duck Run (Box 138, Folder 58)
- Penna. R.R.- Elimination of Flagman, Lodge #753 (Box 138, Folder 59)
- Penna. R.R.- Flagman Being Required to Perform Duties as Brakeman 6 Cars from Rear of Train #23 (Lodge #775) (Box 138, Folder 60)
- Penna. R.R.- Fill-Out Brakeman, Doc. 16262 (Box 138, Folder 61)
- Penna. R.R.- Flagmen Removed from Helper Engine Crews- Phila.-Phoenixville (Box 138, Folder 62)
- Penna. R.R.- General Order No. 1104 (Train Signals) (Box 138, Folder 63)
- Penna. R.R.- Hazardous, Unprotected Railroad Crossing at Plymouth Meeting (Box 138, Folder 64)
- P.U.C.- Accident Reports (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Penna. R.R.- Switch Stands (Rule 8) (Lodge #105) (Box 139, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Material (P.U,C, Cases) (Box 139, Folder 3)
- B.&O. R.R- Walkways & Railings on Bridges Petrolia, Foxburg, & Kane, Pa. (Lodge #591) (Box 139, Folder 4)
- Penna. R.R.- Walkways on E. Altoona Bridge (Lodge #174) C. 17573 (Box 139, Folder 5)
- Penna. R.R.- Walkways & Railings on O.C. Bridge and Bridge No. 28.32 (Lodges #299 and #753) (Box 139, Folder 6)
- Reading R.R.- Exemption of Certain Bridges From Provisions of Commission's Order, i.e., Self-Illuminating Lamps on Certain Switch Stands, Sidewalks, and Railings on Certain Bridges, Etc. (Box 139, Folder 7)
- Union R.R.- Walkways & Railings on Bridges (Port Perry Bridge & Rankin Bridge) (Box 139, Folder 8)
- rule 9 Walkways and Railings on Certain Bridges and Trestles in Penna. (Box 139, Folder 9)
- Wilkes-Barre Conn. R.R.- Walkways and Railings on Bridge, Crossing Susque. River on P.R.R. & D.&H. R.R. (Lodge #153) (Box 139, Folder 10)
- Close Clearances, Debris, Etc.- Reading. Co. (Port Richmond Lodge #956) (Box 139, Folder 11)
- Close Clearances (Stowe Yard)- Reading. Co. (Lodge #665) (Box 139, Folder 12)
- Penna. R.R.- Various Close Clearance and Unsafe Conditions Existing on the P-T Division (Lodge #160) (Box 139, Folder 13)
- Penna. R.R.- Close Clearance Conditions on the Phila. Terminal Div. (Lodge #160) (Box 139, Folder 14)
- Penna. R.R.- Various Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions- Lodge #160, Phila. (Box 139, Folder 15)
- Close Clearance- Reading. R.R. Fifth St. Yard Reading, Pa. (Box 139, Folder 16)
- Close Clearance- Lehigh Valley R.R. (Packerton East Bound Yard- Lodge #292) (Box 139, Folder 17)
- Monongahela Connecting R.R. & P.&L.E. R.R.- 34th St. Yard Lodge #553 (Box 139, Folder 18)
- Close Clearance- Parrish Pressed Steel Co., Reading, Pa. (Box 139, Folder 19)
- Close Clearance-P.R.R.-Grays Ferry, Penrose Yard & Girard Point (Switches) (Lodge #160) (Box 139, Folder 20)
- Close Clearances- P.R.R.- Newberry, Lock Haven, and Wmpst. Freight House (Box 139, Folder 21)
- Close Clearance -P.R.R. Paoli Yard- Lodge #511 (Box 139, Folder 22)
- Close Clearance-P.R.R.-Phillipstone Yard-Lodge #258 (Box 139, Folder 23)
- Close Clearance- P.R.R.-Unity Branch Yard-Lodge #159 (Box 139, Folder 24)
- Close Clearance- P.R.R. Wheatland Yard District (Box 139, Folder 25)
- Close Clearance- P.R.R. Northbound Thurlow Yd. Chester, Penna. (Box 139, Folder 26)
- Steelton-Highspire- Unsafe and Unsanitary Conditions (Lodge #42) (Box 139, Folder 27)
- Steelton-Highspire R.R.- Unsafe Conditions Switches (Lodge #42) (Box 139, Folder 28)
- Steelton-Highspire R.R.- Violation of Rule 8 (Equipping Switch Stands with Targets Which Are Self-Illuminated) (Box 139, Folder 29)
- Union R.R.- Caboose Forms (Box 139, Folder 30)
- Union R.R.- Hauling Hot Slag Over an Open Bridge, Over the Monongahela River; Without Protective Covering (Box 139, Folder 31)
- Union R.R.- Inadequate Rear-End Flag Protection- Wilson, Chm., G.G.C. (Box 139, Folder 32)
- Upper Merion & Plymouth R.R.- Installation and Use of a Gyro-Lite on Locomotive #53 (Box 139, Folder 33)
- Upper Merion-Plymouth R.R.- Unsafe Conditions (Lodge #1079) (Box 139, Folder 34)
- Western Maryland R.R.- Abandonment of a Portion of its Somerset Subdivision Line, Etc. A.90621 (Box 139, Folder 35)
- Close Clearance- A Yard, at Albion, Pa. (Box 139, Folder 36)
- Close Clearance- B&O RR and PRR in Vicinity of New Castle; Lodge 955 (Doc. 16613 & 16623) (Box 139, Folder 37)
- Close Clearance- Etna Yard (Lodge #467) C. 16853 (Box 139, Folder 38)
- Reading R.R.- Discontinuance of Sale of Tickets, Particularly Interline Tickets at Bethlehem (Box 139, Folder 39)
- Reading R.R.- Equipping of Track Cars With Brackets- Ties in With I.D. 54 (Box 139, Folder 40)
- Reading R.R.- Exemption from Part III of P.U.C.'s R.R. Regulations- Overhead Clearances (Box 139, Folder 41)
- Reading R.R.- General Correspondence- A.N. Jewell, Gen. Mgr. (Box 139, Folder 42)
- Reading R.R.- Inadequate Service Lodge #172 (Box 139, Folder 43)
- Reading R.R.- Removal of Red Marker Lights from Automatic Signals- Lodge #131 (Box 139, Folder 44)
- Reading R.R.- Train #32- Reading. & Phila. With One Toilet Facility (lodge #172) (Box 139, Folder 45)
- Reading R.R.- Unsafe and Hazardous Conditions at Chester- Lodge #488 (I.C. 3413052) (Box 139, Folder 46)
- Reading R.R.- Unsafe Conditions at Carlisle Jct. (Lodge #127) (Box 139, Folder 47)
- Reading R.R.- Unsafe Conditions Existing at the Reading Yard-Lodge #172 (Box 139, Folder 48)
- Reading R.R.- Unsafe Conditions Lodge #787 (Box 139, Folder 49)
- Reading R.R.- Unsafe Conditions- Self-Illuminated Switches (Lodge #127) (Box 139, Folder 50)
- Reading R.R.- Unsafe Working Conditions at Hershey, Pa. (Lodge #787) (Box 139, Folder 51)
- Reading R.R. & Central R.R. of N.J.- Electric Lights- Catasauqua Yd. & East Penn Jct. (Box 139, Folder 52)
- Red Arrow Lines- Hazardous Conditions on Buses and Trollies (Lodge #998) (Box 139, Folder 53)
- State Wide- Motor Car (I.D. 54) (Box 139, Folder 54)
- I.C.C. Snow Plows on Diesels (Box 140, Folder 1)
- I.C.C. Various Complaints on Defective Equipment (Box 140, Folder 2)
- Public Notices and Orders (Box 140, Folder 3)
- Delaware & Hudson R.R.- Trains Brought Into the Yard and Switched Without Being Inspected (Box 140, Folder 4)
- Delaware, Lackawanna, & Western R.R. Trackage Rights Between Pittston Jct. & Old Forge, Lacka. & Luzerne Counties, Pa. (Box 140, Folder 5)
- Lehigh & New England R.R.- Abandoning the Bangor Branch, Northampton County, Penna. (Box 140, Folder 6)
- Lehigh & New England R.R- Authority to Discontinue Certain Interlocking & Approach Signals- Lansford & Hauto, Pa. (Box 140, Folder 7)
- Lehigh Valley R.R.- Installation of Reflector Discs on Switch Targets at W.B. (Box 140, Folder 8)
- McKeesport Connecting R.R.-N.T.X. Cars, National Tube Company (Box 140, Folder 9)
- New York Central R.R.- Handling of Cars at the Electric Plant, Shawsville, Pa. (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Penna. R.R.- Various Complaints Reported by W.K. Crawford, Lodge #456 (Box 140, Folder 11)
- Reading Company- Backup Movement from "A" to "B' (Box 140, Folder 12)
- Wellsville, Addison & Galeton Railroad Corp.- Purchase and Control (Box 140, Folder 13)
- I.C.C.- Reporting Rule Changes (Box 140, Folder 14)
- I.C.C.-Accident Reports-Journals (Box 140, Folder 15)
- I.C.C.- (Reports & Accidents) Penna. 1950-1966 (Box 140, Folder 16)